malaysiajobs.biz 2016-01-12

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for www.malaysiajobs.biz**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at malaysiajobs@ymail.com.

At www.malaysiajobs.biz, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.malaysiajobs.biz and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.malaysiajobs.biz makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.malaysiajobs.biz does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.malaysiajobs.biz.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.malaysiajobs.biz and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.malaysiajobs.biz send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.malaysiajobs.biz has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.malaysiajobs.biz’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Disclaimer**  
The materials on MalaysiaJobs.biz are provided “as is”. MalaysiaJobs.biz makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, MalaysiaJobs.biz does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

**Limitations**  
In no event shall MalaysiaJobs.biz or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on MalaysiaJobs.biz’s Internet site, even if MalaysiaJobs.biz authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

**Revisions and Errata**  
The materials appearing on MalaysiaJobs.biz’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. MalaysiaJobs.biz does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. MalaysiaJobs.biz may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. MalaysiaJobs.biz does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.

**Links**  
MalaysiaJobs.biz has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by MalaysiaJobs.biz. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.

**Ownership of Photos and Videos**  
Unless otherwise clearly specified, MalaysiaJobs.biz does not claim ownership of photos and videos used or embedded on the site.
